to me family has always is very very
important
Rachel time for this child married now I
have two daughters family to be as we in
the back door
and family for me is not defined just by
a small nuclear family for me family
means everybody my employees my staff my
business partners my agents my clients
in fact very early on I was taught to
oscillates both of them that means that
the universe is one family world is one
family to me family means everyone and
everybody together and that is why when
I heard that today's international
copied it is good to wish you all and my
this culture reinforced my belief that
family is positive today with my wife
and my elder daughter Lucia
we wish you a very very happy the victim
getting the arse before getting the
yours
young man yes
[Music]
getting liaise is something oka
family cars Hey
be friendly Hey
getting me you're getting me getting me
yours give me yours
[Music]
you